A Guide to the Virginia Auditor of Public Accounts - Tobacco and Flour Inspector Records, 1776-1878
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
A Guide to the Virginia Auditor of Public Accounts - Tobacco and Flour Inspector Records, 1776-1878
The Library of Virginia
APA 296, APA 297, APA 298, APA 299
15.65 cu. ft. (33 boxes)
Virginia Auditor of Public Accounts (1776-1928)
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no access restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Transferred from the Auditor of Public Accounts in 1913.
Biographical Information
The General Assembly passed an act regulating the inspection of tobacco during its session begun in October 1777. Inspectors were nominated by county courts and commissioned by the governor. They inspected and graded tobacco, weighed hogsheads, and maintained record of the movement of tobacco in and out of public warehouses. Owners of tobacco were entitled to reimbursement for property destroyed in ware house fires upon certification by the inspectors. Periodic reports were made by inspectors to the auditor of public accounts.
During its session begun in October 1776 the General Assembly passed an act authorizing the county courts to appoint inspectors to examine barrels of flour prior to sale. Subsequent acts made the inspection system more elaborate: inspectors weighed each barrel and stamped it with the place of inspection, the quality of the flour, and the name of the miller. Periodic reports were made first to the treasurer and later to the auditor of public accounts.
Scope and Content
Tobacco and Flour Inspector records, 1776-1878, including tobacco and flour inspector returns, tobacco manifests, tobacco claims, tobacco duty affidavits, tobacco ledgers and miscellaneous correspondence and loose records. The majority of the records pertain to tobacco inspector records, with only Series II relating to flour inspector records.
The records are arranged into 8 series. This collection consists of several Auditor of Public Accounts (APA) accessions that while identified separately, all pertain to the same collection of records. Since the specific APA accession numbers have been used and referenced over the years it was decided that each series would reference it's specific APA number, but one finding aid would describe the entire collection.
Arrangement
Series I: Tobacco Inspector returns, 1776-1878 (APA 296)
Series II: Flour Inspector returns, 1794-1858 (APA 296)
Series III: Tobacco manifests, 1789-1809 (APA 296)
Series IV: Burned tobacco claims, 1776-1858 (APA 296)
Series V: Correspondence and loose records, 1777-1866 (APA 296)
Series VI: Tobacco Inspectors book, 1781-1782 (APA 297)
Series VII: Ledger of accounts with tobacco inspectors, 1781-1789 (APA 298)
Series VIII: Tobacco duty affidavits for refund or surplus, 1787-1790 (APA 299)
Contents List
- Series I: Tobacco Inspector returns, 1776-1878 (APA 296)., Extent: 23 boxes (10.35 cu. ft.). (Box 1-23)
  Tobacco Inspector returns, 1776-1878, are housed in 23 boxes, and are arranged alphabetically by warehouse name. These returns consist of accounts with the Commonwealth for expenses incurred for salaries, supplies (such as scales, paper, books, marking irons and ink), and services (adjusting weights and marking irons), and also include amounts of tobacco received/inspected/on hand/shipped for the reporting period, and the names of the tobacco inspectors. Some of the returns are also accompanied by lists of tobacco received and/or shipped which may include date, amount of tobacco received/sold/shipped, name (who shipped by), vessel name, and to whom sold/delivered/name of ship commander. This series may also include receipts, vouchers, and a small amount of correspondence.
  Alphabetically by warehouse name.
  - Alexandria Warehouse (Fairfax County), 1780-1794, 1799-1801. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Amherst Warehouse (Amherst County), 1792-1793, 1795-1799. (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Amherst Warehouse (Amherst County), 1799-1803. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Amherst Warehouse (Amherst County), 1803-1812. (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Amherst Warehouse (Amherst County), 1812-1829. (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Anderson's Warehouse (Halifax County), 1801-1811, 1817-1826, 1831-1832. (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Aquia Warehouse (Stafford County), 1782-1787. (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Aquia Warehouse (Stafford County), 1787-1791. (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Aquia Warehouse (Stafford County), 1791-1799, 1902-1809. (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Aylett's and Todd's (King William County), 1777-1778, 1782-1806, 1821-1822. (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Barksdale's Warehouse (Dinwiddie County), 1782-1787. (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Beckwith's Warehouse (Richmond County), 1782-1783. (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Blackwater's Warehouse (Campbell County), 1806-1825, 1829-1933. (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Blandford's Warehouse (Prince George County), 1780-1788. (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Blandford's Warehouse (Prince George County), 1788-1797. (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Blandford's Warehouse (Prince George County), 1797-1817. (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - John Bolling's Warehouse (Chesterfield County), 1779-1800. (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - John Bolling's Warehouse (Chesterfield County), 1800-1811. (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Bolling Point/Robert Bolling's Warehouse (Dinwiddie County/Petersburg), 1780-1799, 1803. (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Bollingbrook Warehouse (Dinwiddie County/Petersburg), 1780-1785. (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Bollingbrook Warehouse (Dinwiddie County/Petersburg), 1785-1796. (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Bollingbrook Warehouse (Dinwiddie County/Petersburg), 1796-1807. (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Bollingbrook Warehouse (Dinwiddie County/Petersburg), 1807-1823. (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Boon's and Collier's Warehouse (unknown location), 1789-1790. (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Boswell's Warehouse (Dinwiddie County), 1807-1825. (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Bowler's and Piscattaway's Warehouse (Essex County), 1780-1781. (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Bowler's Warehouse (Essex County), 1781-1796. (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Boyd's Warehouse (Prince George County), 1777, 1780-1794. (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Boyd's Warehouse (Prince George County), 1794-1808, 1810-1816. (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Boyd's Hole and Machodack's Warehouses (King George County), 1778, 1781-1786. (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Boyd's Hole and Machodack's Warehouses (King George County), 1787-1809, 1814. (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Brickhouse Warehouse (New Kent County), 1783-1791. (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Brookneal's Warehouse (Campbell County), 1818-1820. (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Byrd's Warehouse (Henrico County/Richmond), 1777-1789. (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Byrd's Warehouse (Henrico County/Richmond), 1789-1797. (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Byrd's Warehouse (Henrico County/Richmond), 1797-1807. (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Byrd's Warehouse (Henrico County/Richmond), 1807-1814, 1831. (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Camden's Warehouse (Amherst County/Nelson County), 1797-1823. (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Campbell's Warehouse (Jefferson County), 1797-1823. (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Cannon's Warehouse (Buckingham County), 1795-1820. (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Catpoint Warehouse (Richmond County), 1782-1795. (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Catpoint Warehouse (Richmond County), 1795-1803, 1812. (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Cedarpoint Warehouse (Dinwiddie County/Petersburg), 1780-1781, 1784-1799. (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Cedarpoint Warehouse (Dinwiddie County/Petersburg), 1799-1824. (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Centre Warehouse (Petersburg), 1842-1858. (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Centre Warehouse (Petersburg), 1858-1864. (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Cherrystone and Nassadox Warehouse (Northampton County), 1784-1787. (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Claiborne's Warehouse (Pittsylvania County/Danville), 1818-1819, 1823-1834. (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Coan's Warehouse (Northumberland County), 1781-1800. (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Coan's Warehouse (Northumberland County), 1800-1812, 1814-1819. (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Colchester Warehouse (Fairfax County), 1777, 1781, 1783-1789. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Colchester Warehouse (Fairfax County), 1789-1805. (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Cottage Landing Warehouse (James City County), 1784-1800. (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Cross Street Warehouse (Petersburg), 1806-1825. (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Crow's Warehouse (Botetourt County), 1791-1794. (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Crutchfield's Warehouse (also known as Page's Warehouse) (Hanover County), 1777. (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Curd's Warehouse (Mercer County), 1788-1791. (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Curd's Warehouse (Buckingham County), 1825-1835. (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Danville Warehouse (Pittsylvania County), 1817-1818. (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Davis' Warehouse (Prince George County), 1780-1790. (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Davis' Warehouse (Prince George County), 1790-1805. (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Davis' Warehouse (Prince George County), 1805-1825. (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Davis and Lowry's Warehouse (Lancaster County), 1781-1810. (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Deacon's Neck Warehouse (Gloucester County), 1780-1797. (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Deacon's Neck Warehouse (Gloucester County), 1797-1816. (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Deane's Warehouse (Cumberland County), 1798-1813, 1816-1824. (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Deep Creek and Glasscock's Warehouse (Lancaster County), 1777, 1781-1792. (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Deep Creek and Glasscock's Warehouse (Lancaster County), 1792-1802, 1804-1812. (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Denbigh Warehouse (Warwick County), 1783-1787, 1790. (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Dibrell's Warehouse (Richmond City), 1857-1859. (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Dibrell's Warehouse (Richmond City), 1860-1864. (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Dixon's Warehouse (Stafford County), 1782-1793. (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Dixon's Warehouse (Stafford County), 1793-1805. (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Dixon's Warehouse (Stafford County), 1805-1811, 1814-1824. (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Dumfries Warehouse (Prince Willia. County), 1781-1789. (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Dumfries Warehouse (Prince William County), 1789-1795. (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Dunkirk Warehouse (Halifax County), 1796-1799. (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Epperson's Warehouse (Buckingham County), 1803-1804. (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Falls of Potomac Warehouse (Fairfax County), 1783-1791. (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Falls of Potomac Warehouse (Fairfax County), 1791-1800. (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Falmouth Warehouse (Stafford County), 1777, 1781-1796. (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Farmville Warehouse (Prince Edward County), 1820-1845, 1849-1851, 1853-1857, 1863-1864. (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Fredericksburg Warehouse (Spotsylvania County), 1783-1793. (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Fredericksburg Warehouse (Spotsylvania County), 1793-1806. (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Fredericksburg Warehouse (Spotsylvania County), 1806-1821. (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Fredericksburg Warehouse (Spotsylvania County), 1821-1834, 1836, 1858-1860. (Box 7)
  - Friend's Warehouse (Campbell County), 1808-1824. (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Friend's Warehouse (Campbell County), 1924-1844. (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Friend's Warehouse (Campbell County), 1844-1855. (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Friend's Warehouse (Campbell County), 1855-1864. (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Gibson's Warehouse (King George County), 1775-1777, 1780-1781, 1784-1796. (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Gibson's Warehouse (King George County), 1796-1813. (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Glascock's Warehouse (Richmond County), 1781-1783, 1808-1809, 1813-1815. (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Gray's Creek Warehouse (Surry County), 1780-1781, 1784-1804. (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Hampton Warehouse (Elizabeth City County), 1784-1792. (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Henderson's Warehouse (albemarle County), 1791-1801. (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Henderson' and Randolph's Warehouse (Albemarle County), 1801-1812, 1821. (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - High Street Warehouse (Petersburg / Dinwiddie County), 1791-1807. (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - High Street Warehouse (Petersburg / Dinwiddie County), 1807-1824. (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Hobb's Hole Warehouse (Essex County), 1781-1787. (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Hobb's Hole Warehouse (Essex County), 1787-1795, 1798, 1800-1802, 1805-1808. (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Holland's Warehouse (Danville), 1867. (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Hood's Warehouse (Prince George County), 1785-1792. (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Horseley's Warehouse (Buckingham County), 1792-1804. (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Horseley's Warehouse (Buckingham County), 1804-1816. (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Horseley's Warehouse (Buckingham County), 1817-1829. (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Indian Creek and Dymer's Warehouse (Lancaster County), 1781-1790. (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Indian Creek and Dymer's Warehouse (County), 1790-1810. (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - James River Canal Warehouse (Richmond City), 1804-1810. (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - James River Canal Warehouse (Richmond City), 1810-1816. (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - James River Canal Warehouse (Richmond City), 1816-1823. (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - James River Canal Warehouse (Richmond City), 1823-1828. (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - James River Canal Warehouse (Richmond City), 1828-1834. (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - James River Canal Warehouse (Richmond City) - Accounts and warrants, 1801-1803. (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - James River Canal Warehouse (Richmond City) - Accounts and warrants, 1804-1807. (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Johnson's Warehouse (Chesterfield County), 1791-1797. (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Johnson's Warehouse (Chesterfield County), 1797-1812. (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Johnson's Warehouse (Chesterfield County), 1812-1821. (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Johnson's Warehouse (Chesterfield County), 1821-1831. (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Kemp's Warehouse (Middlesex County), 1789-1795, 1798-1799. (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Kennon's Warehouse (Charles City County), 1784-1785. (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Kinsale Warehouse (Westmoreland County), 1822. (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Layton's Warehouse (Essex County), 1784-1796. (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Leeds and Mattox Warehouse (Westmoreland County), 1781-1782, 1786-1799. (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Liberty Warehouse (Campbell County / Lynchburg), 1806-1824. (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Liberty Warehouse (Campbell County / Lynchburg), 1824-1841. (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Liberty Warehouse (Campbell County / Lynchburg), 1841-1854. (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Liberty Warehouse (Campbell County / Lynchburg), 1854-1865. (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Linn's Warehouse (Pittsylvania County), 1833-1841. (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Littlepage's Warehouse (New Kent County), 1780-1793. (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Lowpoint Warehouse (Surry County), 1783-1797, 1802-1803. (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Lynch's Warehouse (Campbell County), 1787-1792. (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Lynch's Warehouse (Campbell County), 1792-1800. (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Lynch's Warehouse (Campbell County), 1800-1806. (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Lynch's Warehouse (Campbell County), 1806-1818. (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Lynch's Warehouse (Campbell County), 1818-1835. (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Lynch's Warehouse (Campbell County), 1835-1853. (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Lynch's Warehouse (Campbell County), 1858-1859, 1861. (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Lynchburg Warehouse (Lynchburg), 1822. (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - McRae's Warehouse (Dinwiddie County), 1808-1825. (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Manchester Warehouse (Chesterfield County), 1785-1796. (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Manchester Warehouse (Chesterfield County), 1796-1810. (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Manchster Warehouse (Chesterfield County), 1810-1828. (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Mantapike and Frazier's Warehouse (King William County), 1777, 1781-1789. (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Mantapike and Frazier's Warehouse (King William County), 1789-1811. (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Martin's Warehouse (Campbell County / Lynchburg), 1803-1824. (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Martin's Warehouse (Campbell County / Lynchburg), 1824-1840. (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Martin's Warehouse (Campbell County / Lynchburg), 1840-1857. (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Martin's Warehouse (Campbell County / Lynchburg), 1858-1862, 1864. (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Mattox Warehouse (Westmoreland County), 1775-1778. (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Mayo's Warehouse (Richmond), 1859-1861. (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Mayo's Warehouse (Richmond), 1861-1864. (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Meadsville Warehouse (Halifax County), 1804. (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Meriwether's Warehouse (Hanover County), 1777-1778, 1782-1795. (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Milner's Warehouse (Nansemond County / Suffolk), 1784-1806. (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Moon's Warehouse (Albemarle County / Scottsville), 1832. (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Moore's Warehouse (Petersburg), 1803-1825. (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Moore's Warehouse (Petersburg), 1825-1850. (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Moore's Warehouse (Petersburg), 1850-1857. (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Moore's Warehouse (Petersburg), 1857-1864, 1872. (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Neal's Warehouse (Danville), 1859-1864. (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Nicholas' Warehouse (Albemarle County), 1790-1793, 1796-1811, 1818. (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Nominy Warehouse (Westmoreland County), 1780-1784, 1786-1801. (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Oaks Warehouse (Petersburg), 1808-1828. (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Oaks Warehouse (Petersburg), 1828-1843. (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Oaks Warehouse (Petersburg), 1843-1856. (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Oaks Warehouse (Petersburg), 11856-1859. (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Oaks Warehouse (Petersburg), 1859-1864. (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Osborne's Warehouse (Chesterfield County), 1782-1790. (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Osborne's Warehouse (Chesterfield County), 1790-1796. (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Page's Warehouse (Hanover County), 1777, 1783-1788. (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Page's Warehouse (Hanover County), 1788-1798. (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Pannell's Warehouse (Pittsylvania County), 1818-1825, 1828-1839. (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Petersburg Warehouse (Petersburg / Dinwiddie County), 1784-1794. (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Petersburg Warehouse (Petersburg / Dinwiddie County), 1794-1815. (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Petersburg Warehouse (Petersburg / Dinwiddie County), 1815-1835. (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Pitts, Guilford, and Pungoteague Warehouse (Accomack County), 1781-1788. (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Planters Warehouse (Campbell County / Lynchburg), 1807-1824. (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Planters Warehouse (Campbell County / Lynchburg), 1824-1845. (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Planters Warehouse (Campbell County / Lynchburg), 1845-1864. (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Pohick Warehouse (Fairfax County), 1778. (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Poropotank Warehouse (Gloucester County), 1781-1789, 1791-1799. (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Portsmouth Warehouse (Norfolk County), 1786-1789. (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Potomac River Warehouse (Alexandria County), 1846-1850. (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Powhatan Warehouse (City of Richmond), 1805-1812. (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Quantico Warehouse (Prince William County), 1783-1791. (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Quantico Warehouse (Prince William County), 1791-1799. (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Quantico Warehouse (Prince William County), 1799-1811. (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Quantico Warehouse (Prince William County), 1811-1822. (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Randolph's Warehouse (Prince Edward County), 1799-1805, 1817-1833. (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Randolph's Warehouse (Prince Edward County), 1833-1866. (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Rappahannock Warehouse (Unknown County), 1782. (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Richmond Public Warehouse (City of Richmond), 1832-1842. (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Richmond Public Warehouse (City of Richmond), 1842-1849. (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Richmond Public Warehouse (City of Richmond), 1849-1856. (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Richmond Public Warehouse (City of Richmond), 1856-1858. (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Richmond Public Warehouse (City of Richmond), 1858-1860. (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Richmond Public Warehouse (City of Richmond), 1860-1864, 1878. (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Rivanna Warehouse (Fluvanna County), 178601803. (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Rivanna Warehouse (Fluvanna County), 1803-1820. (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Rockett's Warehouse (Ciyt of Richmond), 1783-1789. (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Rockett's Warehouse (City of Richmond), 1789-1802. (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Rockett's Warehouse (City of Richmond), 1802-1814. (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Rocky Ridge Warehouse (Henrico County / City of Richmond), 1782-1793. (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Rosegill's Warehouse (Middlesex County), 1797-1805, 1809-1810. (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Roy's Warehouse (Caroline County), 1782-1791. (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Roy's Warehouse (Caroline County), 1791-1798. (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Royster's Warehouse (Mecklenburg County), 1818-1821, 1831-1833, 1835-1840. (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Royster's Warehouse (Mecklenburg County), 1840-1858. (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Royston's Warehouse (Spotsylvania County / Fredericksburg), 1777, 1780-1783. (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Royston's Warehouse (Spotsylvania County / Fredericksburg), 1784-1788. (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Royston's Warehouse (Spotsylvania County / Fredericksburg), 1788-1796. (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Royston's Warehouse (Spotsylvania County / Fredericksburg), 1796-1807. (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Royston's Warehouse (Spotsylvania County / Fredericksburg), 1807-1813. (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Saint Tammany Warehouse (Mecklenburg County), 1792-1802. (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Seabrook's Warehouse (Henrico County / City of Richmond), 1810-1824. (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Seabrook's Warehouse (Henrico County / City of Richmond), 1824-1840. (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Seabrook's Warehouse (Henrico County / City of Richmond), 1840-1848. (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Seabrook's Warehouse (Henrico County / City of Richmond), 1848-1852. (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Seabrook's Warehouse (Henrico County / City of Richmond), 1853-1856. (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Seabrook's Warehouse (Henrico County / City of Richmond), 1856-1859. (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Seabrook's Warehouse (Henrico County / City of Richmond), 1859-1861. (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Shepherd's Warehouse (King and Queen County), 1784-1791. (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Shepherd's Warehouse (King and Queen County), 1791-1806, 1810-1811. (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Shockoe Warehouse (Henrico County / City of Richmond), 1777, 1780-1785. (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Shockoe Warehouse (Henrico County / City of Richmond), 1785-1791. (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Shockoe Warehouse (Henrico County / City of Richmond), 1791-1804. (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Shockoe Warehouse (Henrico County / City of Richmond), 1804-1811. (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Shockoe Warehouse (Henrico County / City of Richmond), 1811-1820. (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Shockoe Warehouse (Henrico County / City of Richmond), 1820-1830. (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Shockoe Warehouse (Henrico County / City of Richmond), 1830-1840. (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Shockoe Warehouse (Henrico County / City of Richmond), 1840-1848. (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Shockoe Warehouse (Henrico County / City of Richmond), 1848-1854. (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Shockoe Warehouse (Henrico County / City of Richmond), 1855-1856. (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Shockoe Warehouse (Henrico County / City of Richmond), 1857. (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Shockoe Warehouse (Henrico County / City of Richmond), 1858. (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Shockoe Warehouse (Henrico County / City of Richmond), 1859. (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Shockoe Warehouse (Henrico County / City of Richmond), 1860. (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Shockoe Warehouse (Henrico County / City of Richmond), 1861. (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Shockoe Warehouse (Henrico County / City of Richmond), 1861-1864. (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Smithfield Warehouse (Isle of Wight County), 1784-1796. (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - South Quay Warehouse (Nansemond County / Suffolk), 1781-1782, 1786-1793. (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Spring Warehouse (Campbell County / Lynchburg), 1793-1795. (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Spring Warehouse (Campbell County / Lynchburg), 1795-1797. (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Spring Warehouse (Campbell County / Lynchburg), 1798-1800. (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Spring Warehouse (Campbell County / Lynchburg), 1800-1802. (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Spring Warehouse (Campbell County / Lynchburg), 1802-1810. (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Spring Warehouse (Campbell County / Lynchburg), 1810-1824. (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Spring Warehouse (Campbell County / Lynchburg), 1824-1838. (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Stafford Warehouse (Stafford County), 1818. (Box 20, Folder 10)